Guide to the Katharine Buell Wilder Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Additions since 1987, 1764-1996
  - December 2015 Acquisition, 1764–1996; 1.25 linear feet (3 boxes)
    - Family papers
      - Susanna Wilder Heinz family papers, 1880–1987 (Box 45, Folder 584)
        Correspondence between Susanna and Kathryn K. Conners, 1985- 1987; memorial service for Elizabeth Buell September 5, 1985; copy of revocable trust for Elizabeth Buell
      - "The Pawned Ring- Proposal New England Style" manuscript and correspondence, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 585)
        "The Pawned Ring Proposal- New England Style, 1880" story written by Bernard Heinz and rejection letter from Yankee Magazine, undated; photocopied letters from Fred to Abbie, undated; typescript of letter from Fred Wilder to Miss. A. G. Holman, June 27, 1880
      - Buell family correspondence, 1937–1987 (Box 45, Folder 586)
      - Copies of Abner Kneeland entries in card catalog, undated (Box 45, Folder 587)
      - Contents from the Book of Wilders, undated (Box 45, Folder 588)
      - Robert Wilder and Katharine Buell Wilders' writings, undated (Box 45, Folder 589)
      - Wilder Family Photographs (2 folders), 1896–1899 (Box 45, Folder 590-591)